<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Education Career Consultant</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="consulting_scope">The importance of consulting is multifaceted and extends to various aspects of personal, societal, and global development. Here are several key reasons why consulting is of utmost importance:

Knowledge Transfer: Consulting is the primary means through which knowledge, expertise, and best practices are shared from experienced professionals to those seeking guidance. It ensures that valuable insights and solutions are passed on to address complex problems and challenges.

Skill Development: Consulting equips individuals and organizations with the skills and strategies they need to excel in their endeavors. Whether it\'s strategic planning, process improvement, or problem-solving, consulting plays a pivotal role in skill development.

Personal and Professional Growth: Consulting fosters personal and professional growth by offering guidance and mentorship. It encourages individuals to expand their knowledge, improve their decision-making abilities, and enhance their career prospects.

Empowerment: Consulting empowers individuals and organizations by providing them with the knowledge and expertise necessary to make informed decisions. It enables people to navigate complex issues, make strategic choices, and achieve their goals effectively.

Business and Organizational Success: Consulting is essential for the success of businesses and organizations. It offers expert insights and recommendations that can lead to improved performance, increased profitability, and sustainable growth.

Innovation and Problem Solving: Consulting is a catalyst for innovation and problem-solving. It brings fresh perspectives and ideas to the table, helping organizations overcome challenges, adapt to changing environments, and innovate in their fields.

Global Reach: In an interconnected world, consulting promotes global reach by providing access to international expertise and market insights. It encourages organizations to think globally and expand their operations across borders.

Community and Network Building: Consulting strengthens communities and professional networks by fostering collaboration and knowledge exchange. It often serves as a bridge between individuals and organizations, facilitating connections and partnerships.

Economic Development: A well-informed and strategic approach to consulting can contribute significantly to economic development. It helps businesses thrive, attracts investments, and stimulates economic activity.

Quality of Life: Consulting can enhance the quality of life for individuals and communities by addressing critical issues, improving services, and optimizing resource allocation.

Environmental Sustainability: Consulting can promote environmental stewardship and sustainability by advising on eco-friendly practices, resource conservation, and sustainable business models.

Health and Well-being: Consulting can have a positive impact on health and well-being by offering guidance on healthcare strategies, wellness programs, and healthcare system improvements.

In conclusion, consulting is the cornerstone of informed decision-making, problem-solving, and progress in various domains. It empowers individuals and organizations, drives innovation, and contributes to a brighter and more prosperous future for all. As such, investing in quality consulting services and valuing the expertise of consultants is essential for the well-being and success of individuals and society as a whole.</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_account_sign_up"><font color="#FF000000">Don\'t have account?</font> <font color="#FF5722">Sign Up</font></string>
    <string name="matric_scope">Matriculation, or matric for short, is the minimum level of education required to enter college in Pakistan. It is also a prerequisite for most entry level jobs &amp; further study options. Matriculation can be completed in two years through either a government school or a private institution. The government schools in Pakistan are free to attend, but are often overcrowded &amp; have low standards. Private institutions are more expensive but offer better facilities &amp; teaching staff.</string>
    <string name="inter_scope">When the question comes of choosing career after 10th many a times students are confused which stream has more scope in the future and where to go for.  All the streams after 10th i.e. Science commerce and Arts all are the best fields and have a good career option and demand.  Many of the students they select the career option under parental pressure or peer pressure.  When career is to be selected a student should seek a career experts advice for the right career selection.  Is advisable for the student to take a psychometrics career aptitude assessment.  The assessments are helpful for to get a glance of one students interest, aptitude, abilities etc. science stream also have a good career option.  Whereas commerce and Arts also have a good career option.  Student who have a good understanding of science and math’s and have an interest they can go for the science.  If you are having interest in the accounting and auditing and finance field or management field they can go for the commerce stream.  If you have an interest in the subjects like History, Geography, Psychology, Languages etc. than you can go for the Arts stream.  Here are some of the other courses which can be done from any of the stream – BBM, BMS, BBA, Hotel Management, Law course, Interior Design, Fashion Design, Graphic Design, Footwear Design etc. you can take the Ideal career Test from career guid.com and post assessment with the report you can take a counseling session from the career expert of career guide.</string>
    <string name="graduation_scope">You have come so far in your academic life, and now it’s high time to take the right career decision as this will eventually pave your way to a bright professional future. Graduation plays a critical role in shaping professional career. After completing graduation, you are supposed to have superior knowledge in a particular stream of education. Today, the job market is expanding at an exponential rate &amp; off-beat jobs are becoming popular. You have multiple career options after graduation like Engineering, Management, Medical, Hospitality, Computer, Information Technology, Healthcare etc.Almost 60% of candidates start looking for job opportunities right after their graduation. Before you choosing the best career after graduation, you need to know growth scope, prospects, competition, availability of jobs in market, work requirements, etc. If you are good in Spoken, you may tend to get better salaries than other candidates. Communication skills and personality make a remarkable difference in overall career development irrespective of nature of work.</string>
    <string-array name="education">
        <item>Matriculation</item>
        <item>Intermediate</item>
        <item>Graduation</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>