<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Education Career Consultant</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_account_sign_up"><font color="#FF000000">Don\'t have account?</font> <font color="#FF5722">Sign Up</font></string>
    <string name="matric_scope">Matriculation, or matric for short, is the minimum level of education required to enter college in Pakistan. It is also a prerequisite for most entry level jobs &amp; further study options. Matriculation can be completed in two years through either a government school or a private institution. The government schools in Pakistan are free to attend, but are often overcrowded &amp; have low standards. Private institutions are more expensive but offer better facilities &amp; teaching staff.</string>
    <string name="inter_scope">When the question comes of choosing career after 10th many a times students are confused which stream has more scope in the future and where to go for.  All the streams after 10th i.e. Science commerce and Arts all are the best fields and have a good career option and demand.  Many of the students they select the career option under parental pressure or peer pressure.  When career is to be selected a student should seek a career experts advice for the right career selection.  Is advisable for the student to take a psychometrics career aptitude assessment.  The assessments are helpful for to get a glance of one students interest, aptitude, abilities etc. science stream also have a good career option.  Whereas commerce and Arts also have a good career option.  Student who have a good understanding of science and math’s and have an interest they can go for the science.  If you are having interest in the accounting and auditing and finance field or management field they can go for the commerce stream.  If you have an interest in the subjects like History, Geography, Psychology, Languages etc. than you can go for the Arts stream.  Here are some of the other courses which can be done from any of the stream – BBM, BMS, BBA, Hotel Management, Law course, Interior Design, Fashion Design, Graphic Design, Footwear Design etc. you can take the Ideal career Test from career guid.com and post assessment with the report you can take a counseling session from the career expert of career guide.</string>
    <string name="graduation_scope">You have come so far in your academic life, and now it’s high time to take the right career decision as this will eventually pave your way to a bright professional future. Graduation plays a critical role in shaping professional career. After completing graduation, you are supposed to have superior knowledge in a particular stream of education. Today, the job market is expanding at an exponential rate &amp; off-beat jobs are becoming popular. You have multiple career options after graduation like Engineering, Management, Medical, Hospitality, Computer, Information Technology, Healthcare etc.Almost 60% of candidates start looking for job opportunities right after their graduation. Before you choosing the best career after graduation, you need to know growth scope, prospects, competition, availability of jobs in market, work requirements, etc. If you are good in Spoken, you may tend to get better salaries than other candidates. Communication skills and personality make a remarkable difference in overall career development irrespective of nature of work.</string>
    <string-array name="education">
        <item>Matriculation</item>
        <item>Intermediate</item>
        <item>Graduation</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>